Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Records, 1837 - 2013
Bentley Historical Library
- Director's Files, 1905-2013
  - Topical Files, 1905-1999
    - 1905-1950
      - Library of Congress Project C-Manuscripts, 1931-1933 (Box 19)
      - Library of International Relations, 1935-1936 (Box 19)
      - Library of Living Philosophers, 1938-1939 (Box 19)
      - Library of Western Thought, Futan University, 1946-1947 (Box 19)
      - Library Practice
        - 1920-1925 (Box 19)
        - 1925-1933 (Box 19)
        - 1933-1935 (Box 19)
        - 1935-1936 (Box 19)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 19)
        - 1937-1938 (Box 19)
        - 1938-1939 (Box 20)
        - 1939-1940 (Box 20)
        - 1940-1941 (Box 20)
        - 1941-1942 (Box 20)
        - 1942-1943 (Box 20)
        - 1943-1944 (Box 20)
        - 1944-1945 (Box 20)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 20)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 20)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 20)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 20)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 20)
      - Library Privileges
        - 1919-1925 (Box 20)
        - 1925-1930 (Box 20)
        - 1932-1933 (Box 20)
        - 1933-1939 (Box 20)
        - 1939-1943 (Box 20)
        - 1943-1945 (Box 20)
        - 1945-1949 (Box 20)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 20)
      - Library Quarterly
        - 1930-1934 (Box 20)
        - 1934-1939 (Box 20)
      - Library Questionnaires
        - 1907-1920 (Box 20)
        - 1920-1925 (Box 20)
        - 1925-1926 (Box 20)
        - 1926-1930 (Box 20)
        - 1930-1933 (Box 20)
        - 1933-1934 (Box 20)
        - 1934-1935 (Box 20)
        - 1935-1936 (Box 20)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 20)
        - 1937-1938 (Box 20)
        - 1938-1939 (Box 20)
        - 1939-1940 (Box 20)
        - 1940-1942 (Box 20)
        - 1942-1947 (Box 20)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 20)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 20)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 20)
      - Library Review, 1930-1932 (Box 20)
      - Library Rules and Regulations, 1907-1930 (Box 20)
      - Library Staff Associations, 1947-1948 (Box 20)
      - Library Statistics
        - 1905-1908 (Box 20)
        - 1909-1912 (Box 20)
        - 1912-1913 (Box 20)
        - 1914 (Box 20)
        - 1915-1916 (Box 20)
        - 1916-1924 (Box 20)
        - 1925-1930 (Box 21)
        - 1930-1931 (Box 21)
        - 1931-1932 (Box 21)
        - 1932-1933 (Box 21)
        - 1933-1934 (Box 21)
        - 1934-1935 (Box 21)
        - 1935-1936 (Box 21)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 21)
        - 1937-1938 (Box 21)
        - 1938-1942 (Box 21)
        - 1942-1945 (Box 21)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 21)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 21)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 21)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 21)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 21)
      - Library Surveys, 1927-1928 (Box 21)
      - Library Training in Europe, 1932-1933 (Box 21)
      - Library War Work, 1918 (Box 21)
      - Lights
        - 1908-1935 (Box 21)
        - 1927-1950 (Box 21)
      - Lima University, 1947-1948 (Box 21)
      - List of Serial Publications of Foreign Governments, 1927-1930 (Box 21)
      - Little, President, C.C., 1925-1929 (Box 21)
      - Littmann, Enno, 1927-1930 (Box 21)
      - London, Ontario, Public Library, 1918-1923 (Box 21)
      - London University, 1929-1950 (Box 21)
      - Los Angeles Public Library, 1920-1938 (Box 21)
      - Lost Books, 1947-1949 (Box 21)
      - Louisiana State University, 1939-1950 (Box 21)
      - Louisville Free Public Library, 1931-1941 (Box 21)
      - Louvain University
        - 1918-1925 (Box 21)
        - 1927-1933 (Box 21)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 21)
      - Lowe, E.E., 1926-1927 (Box 21)
      - Lucas, Henry S., 1919-1935 (Box 21)
      - Luther College, 1930-1949 (Box 21)
      - Lydenburg, H.M., 1933-1941 (Box 21)
      - Lyon, Lucius, Letters, 1926-1931 (Box 21)
      - McAllister, S.W.
        - 1927-1932 (Box 21)
        - 1932-1933 (Box 21)
        - 1933-1934 (Box 21)
        - 1934-1935 (Box 21)
        - 1935-1936, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - 1936-1937, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - 1937-1938 (Box 21)
        - 1938-1939 (Box 21)
        - 1939-1940 (Box 21)
        - 1940-1941 (Box 21)
        - 1941-1942 (Box 21)
        - 1942-1943 (Box 22)
        - 1943-1944 (Box 22)
        - 1944-1945 (Box 22)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 22)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 22)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 22)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 22)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 22)
      - McAllister, S.W.
        - A.L.A.
          - 1933-1941 (Box 22)
          - 1944-1947 (Box 22)
        - A.L.A. Committee on Constitution and Bylaws, 1935-1938 (Box 22)
        - A.L.A. Committee on Review for Books of Scholarly Nature, 1938-1939 (Box 22)
        - C.C.C. Committee, 1935-1937 (Box 22)
        - Committee on Correspondence Courses, 1938-1939 (Box 22)
        - Memoranda
          - 1934-1935 (Box 22)
          - 1941-1946 (Box 22)
        - Michigan Encyclopedia, 1933-1934 (Box 22)
        - M.L.A.
          - 1934-1936 (Box 22)
          - 1936-1937, 2 folders (Box 22)
          - 1937-1938 (Box 22)
      - McColvin, Lionel R., 1935-1936 (Box 22)
      - McCombs, Charles F., 1911-1912 (Box 22)
      - McGill University
        - 1905-1933 (Box 22)
        - 1933-1941 (Box 22)
      - McGraw Publishing Company, 1907-1910 (Box 22)
      - McGregor Fund, 1938-1939 (Box 22)
      - McGregor, Tracy W., 1933-1937 (Box 22)
      - McGregor, William A., Jr., 1925-1927 (Box 22)
      - McIntosh, A.D., 1939-1940 (Box 22)
      - McKendree College, 1940-1941 (Box 22)
      - MacLean, George E., 1929-1930 (Box 22)
      - McMaster University, 1928-1939 (Box 22)
      - McMurtrie, Douglas C.
        - 1928-1933 (Box 22)
        - 1933-1946 (Box 22)
      - McNitt, V.V., 1927-1941 (Box 22)
      - Madrid University, 1933-1936 (Box 22)
      - Manchester Public Libraries, 1928-1940 (Box 22)
      - Mann, Margaret
        - 1932-1933 (Box 22)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 22)
      - Mansbridge, Albert, 1927-1933 (Box 22)
      - Manual of Historical Literature, 1918-1919 (Box 22)
      - Manuscripts and Papyri
        - [Returned to donor, January 5, 1978], 1924-1935 (Box 22)
        - 1935-1936 (Box 22)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 22)
        - 1937-1938 (Box 22)
        - 1938-1939 (Box 22)
        - 1939-1945 (Box 22)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 22)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 22)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 22)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 22)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 22)
      - Manuscripts, Albert Eid (Box 22)
      - Manuscripts and Papyri preservation, 1923-1924 (Box 22)
      - Maps
        - 1930-1931 (Box 22)
        - 1934-1949 (Box 22)
      - Marietta College, 1910-1924 (Box 22)
      - Markham Pottery, 1911 (Box 22)
      - Marks, James H., 1910 (Box 22)
      - Marquette County Historical Society, 1923-1933 (Box 22)
      - Marquette Public Library, 1923-1924 (Box 22)
      - Marshall Field & Co., 1908-1923 (Box 22)
      - Marshall Jones Co., 1930-1931 (Box 22)
      - Martel, Charles, 1939-1940 (Box 22)
      - Martel, Festschrift, 1930-1931 (Box 22)
      - Martin & Hoyt Co., 1911 (Box 22)
      - Morvellum Co., 1922-1923 (Box 22)
      - Marygrove College, 1931-1947 (Box 22)
      - Mason, William S., 1925-1937 (Box 22)
      - Masonic Literature, 1915-1916 (Box 22)
      - Massachusetts Free Public Library Commission, 1909 (Box 22)
      - Massachusetts General Hospital ', 1907-1912 (Box 22)
      - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1918-1933 (Box 22)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology
        - 1907-1921 (Box 22)
        - 1940-1947 (Box 22)
      - Massachusetts Library Club, 1920-1922 (Box 22)
      - Massachusetts State Library, 1907-1933 (Box 22)
      - Mattice, Harold A., 1928-1938 (Box 22)
      - Medical Information Service, 1915-1916 (Box 22)
      - Medical Librarian, 1919 (Box 22)
      - Medical Library Association
        - 1907-1924 (Box 23)
        - 1925-1934 (Box 23)
        - 1934-1936 (Box 23)
        - 1936-1938 (Box 23)
        - 1938-1950 (Box 23)
      - Melbourne Public Library, 1937-1938 (Box 23)
      - Memoranda, 1915-1917 (Box 23)
      - Memorial Reading Room, 1910-1916 (Box 23)
      - Memorial Tablets, 1908-1910 (Box 23)
      - Merck & Co., 1908 (Box 23)
      - Merriam, G & C, Co., 1909 (Box 23)
      - Merwin-Clayton Sales Co., 1906-1914 (Box 23)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1908-1940 (Box 23)
      - Mexican Librarians, 1927-1928 (Box 23)
      - Mexico. Department of Public Education
        - 1928-1929 (Box 23)
        - 1932-1933 (Box 23)
      - Mexico. National Library, 1928-1940 (Box 23)
      - Mexico. National University, 1920-1929 (Box 23)
      - Meyer, H.H.B., 1932-1936 (Box 23)
      - Miami University, 1904-1930 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Academy of Science, Arts, and Letters
        - 1922-1924 (Box 23)
        - 1924-1925 (Box 23)
        - 1939-1942 (Box 23)
        - 1942-1946 (Box 23)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 23)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 23)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 23)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 23)
        - Hegner Bibliography, 1917 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Agricultural College, 1907-1925 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Alumnus
        - 1908-1925 (Box 23)
        - 1925-1935 (Box 23)
        - 1943-1946 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Central Railroad, 1908-1925 (Box 23)
      - Michigan College of Mines, 1906-1940 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Colleges, 1949-1950 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Daily
        - 1908-1925 (Box 23)
        - 1925-1942 (Box 23)
        - 1943-1950 (Box 23)
        - Official Bulletin, 1946-1950 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Department of Conservation, 1937-1939 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Department of Health, 1933-1947 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Department of Public Instruction, 1922-1947 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Geological Survey, 1906-1914 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Historical Agencies, 1924-1925 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Historical Collections
        - 1937-1944 (Box 23)
        - 1944-1946 (Box 23)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 23)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 23)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Historical Commission
        - 1904-1925 (Box 23)
        - 1925-1935 (Box 23)
        - 1936-1944 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Homeopathic College, 1934-1935 (Box 23)
      - Michigan House of Representatives, 1915 (Box 23)
      - Michigan League
        - 1922-1923 (Box 23)
        - 1926-1931 (Box 23)
        - 1942-1947 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Legislature, 1932-1933 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Librarian
        - 1936-1940 (Box 23)
        - 1940-1949 (Box 23)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 23)
      - Michigan Library Association
        - 1910-1912 (Box 23)
        - 1912-1915 (Box 23)
        - 1915-1920 (Box 23)
        - 1920-1925 (Box 23)
        - 1926-1927 (Box 23)
        - 1927-1928 (Box 24)
        - 1928-1934 (Box 24)
        - 1934-1936 (Box 24)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 24)
        - 1937-1939 (Box 24)
        - 1939-1945 (Box 24)
        - 1945-1947 (Box 24)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 24)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 24)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 24)
        - Ann Arbor Meeting, 1915 (Box 24)
        - Committee on Legislation, 1920-1925 (Box 24)
        - Joint Meeting-Wisconsin Library Association, 1913-1914 (Box 24)
        - Junior Members Round Table, 1939-1940 (Box 24)
        - Planning Committee, 1941-1943 (Box 24)
        - Round Tables, 1926-1927 (Box 24)
        - War Work, 1917-1918 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Library Commission, 1938-1939 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Library Survey, 193T-1939 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Liquor Law, 1919 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project, 1949-1950 (Box 24)
      - Michigan News Index, 1924-1925 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Newspapers, 1925-1926 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Public Libraries
        - 1924-1933 (Box 24)
        - 1934-1948 (Box 24)
      - Michigan School of Religion, 1924-1928 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Schoolmasters Club
        - 1907-1919 (Box 24)
        - 1929-1936 (Box 24)
        - 1936-1950 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Senate
        - 1915 (Box 24)
        - 1934-1940 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Social Welfare Commission, 1943-1944 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Board for Libraries, 1937-1946 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Board of Library Commissioners, 1916-1919 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Federation of Women's Clubs, 1924-1941 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Historical Society, 1936-1937 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Librarian, 1911 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Library
        - 1909-1914 (Box 24)
        - 1915-1925 (Box 24)
        - 1925-1935 (Box 24)
        - 1935-1936 (Box 24)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 24)
        - 1937-1942 (Box 24)
        - 1942-1950 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Medical Society, 1948-1949 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Normal College
        - 1909-1918 (Box 24)
        - 1918-1935 (Box 24)
        - 1937-1941 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Planning Commission, 1934-1935 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Prison, 1926-1936 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Teachers Association, 1908-1920 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Telephone Company, 1909-1925 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State University, 1925-1950 (Box 24)
      - Michigan State Veterinarian, 1925-1926 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Technic, 1911-1917 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Unemployment Compensation Commissions, 1937-1938 (Box 24)
      - Michigan Union, 1926-1935 (Box 24)
      - Michigan University
        - 1904-1908 (Box 24)
        - 1909 (Box 24)
        - 1910, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1911 (Box 25)
        - 1912 (Box 25)
        - 1913, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1914, 5 folders (Box 25)
        - 1915, 3 folders (Box 25)
        - 1916, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1917-1920 (Box 25)
        - 1917, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1918, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1919, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1919-1920, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1920-1921, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1921-1922, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1922-1925 (Box 25)
      - Michigan University
        - Advisers of Women, 1926-1929 (Box 25)
        - Advisory Committee on Alumni Relations, 1932-1936 (Box 25)
        - Advisory Committee on Near East Research, 1929-1930 (Box 25)
        - Allegan County Workshop, 1942-1943 (Box 25)
        - Alumni
          - 1920-1933 (Box 25)
          - 1933-1942 (Box 25)
          - Philadelphia Club, 1929-1935 (Box 25)
          - Reading Lists, 1930-1937 (Box 25)
          - Relations, 1929-1931 (Box 25)
        - Alumni Association
          - 1925-1935 (Box 25)
          - 1935-1944 (Box 25)
          - 1948-1950 (Box 25)
        - Assistant Secretary
          - 1922-1925 (Box 25)
          - 1925-1936 (Box 25)
        - Audio-Visual Education Center
          - 1948-1949 (Box 25)
          - 1949-1950 (Box 25)
        - Binding Department
          - 1919-1920 (Box 26)
          - 1932-1943 (Box 26)
          - 1944-1946 (Box 26)
          - 1947-1949 (Box 26)
        - Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics, 1949-1950 (Box 26)
        - Broadcasting Service, 1930-1946 (Box 26)
        - Buildings and Grounds
          - 1916-1917 (Box 26)
          - 1919-1920 (Box 26)
          - 1920-1928 (Box 26)
          - 1929-1930 (Box 26)
          - 1930-1935 (Box 26)
          - 1935-1937 (Box 26)
          - 1937-1946 (Box 26)
        - Bureau of Alumni Relations, 1930-1948 (Box 26)
        - Bureau of Appointments, 1929-1940 (Box 26)
        - Bureau of Cooperation with Educational Institutions
          - 1933-1935 (Box 26)
          - 1935-1946 (Box 26)
        - Bureau of Government
          - 1923-1945 (Box 26)
          - 1946-1950 (Box 26)
        - Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1937-1950 (Box 26)
        - Bureau of Psychological Services
          - 1946-1947 (Box 26)
          - 1948-1949 (Box 26)
        - Bureau of School Services, 1948-1950 (Box 26)
        - Business Office
          - 1931-1935 (Box 26)
          - 1935-1942 (Box 26)
          - 1942-1946 (Box 26)
          - 1946-1947 (Box 26)
          - 1947-1950 (Box 26)
        - By-Laws
          - 1930-1931 (Box 26)
          - 1938-1942 (Box 26)
        - Calendar
          - 1908-1912 (Box 26)
          - 1926-1927 (Box 26)
          - 1948-1949 (Box 26)
        - Centennial Celebration, 1936-1937 (Box 26)
        - Center for Japanese Studies, 1948-1950 (Box 26)
        - Civil Officers Training School, 1942-1945 (Box 26)
        - Class Officers Council, 1932-1933 (Box 26)
        - College of Architecture
          - 1923-1933 (Box 26)
          - 1935-1944 (Box 26)
          - 1944-1949 (Box 26)
        - College of Dental Surgery, 1922-1927 (Box 26)
        - College of Engineering
          - 1923-1935 (Box 26)
          - 1935-1942 (Box 26)
          - 1943-1947 (Box 26)
          - 1948-1950 (Box 26)
        - College of Literature, Science, and the Arts
          - 1922-1926 (Box 26)
          - 1926-1929 (Box 26)
          - 1929-1933 (Box 26)
          - 1933-1935 (Box 26)
          - 1935-1936 (Box 26)
          - 1936-1937, 2 folders (Box 26)
          - 1937-1938 (Box 27)
          - 1938-1939 (Box 27)
          - 1939-1940 (Box 27)
          - 1940-1941 (Box 27)
          - 1941-1942 (Box 27)
          - 1942-1943 (Box 27)
          - 1943-1945 (Box 27)
          - 1945-1947 (Box 27)
          - 1947-1948 (Box 27)
          - 1948-1949 (Box 27)
          - 1949-1950 (Box 27)
          - Library Committee
            - 1933-1934 (Box 27)
            - 1934-1935 (Box 27)
            - 1935-1936 (Box 27)
            - 1936-1937 (Box 27)
            - 1937-1938 (Box 27)
            - 1938-1939 (Box 27)
            - 1939-1940 (Box 27)
            - 1940-1941 (Box 27)
            - 1941-1942 (Box 27)
            - 1943-1944 (Box 27)
            - 1944-1945 (Box 27)
            - 1945-1946 (Box 27)
            - 1946-1947 (Box 27)
            - 1947-1948 (Box 27)
            - 1948-1949 (Box 27)
            - 1949-1950 (Box 27)
        - College of Pharmacy
          - 1922-1944 (Box 27)
          - 1949-1952 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Admissions Policy, 1945-1946 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Alumni Relations, 1929-1940 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Chinese Cultural Scholarships, 1944-1945 (Box 27)
        - Committee on College Curriculum, 1926-1927 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Cooperation between Michigan Colleges of Education and the University
          - 1937-1940 (Box 27)
          - 1940-1942 (Box 27)
          - 1942-1946 (Box 27)
          - 1946-1947 (Box 27)
          - 1947-1948 (Box 27)
          - 1948-1949 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Correspondence Courses
          - 1927-1942 (Box 27)
          - 1942-1943 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Defense Issues, 1940-1941 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Dormitory Libraries, 1944-1945 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Educational Policies, 1940-1941 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Endowments, 1926-1927 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Faculty Research, 1932-1933 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Fees, 1944-1946 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Honors convocation, 1936-1941 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Latin American Relations, 1942-1943 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Memberships in Educational Associations, 1938-1939 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Michigan Dutch Celebration, 1947 (Box 27)
        - Committee on National Defense, 1941-1942 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Near East Research
          - 1926-1927 (Box 27)
          - 1927-1928 (Box 27)
        - Committee on Occupational Deferment
          - 1941-1944 (Box 28)
          - 1944-1945 (Box 28)
          - 1945-1946 (Box 28)
        - Committee on Office Personnel
          - 1931-1932 (Box 28)
          - 1933-1941 (Box 28)
        - Committee on Plant and Equipment
          - 1931-1933 (Box 28)
          - 1933-1934 (Box 28)
        - Committee on Program and Policy, 1931-1932 (Box 28)
        - Committee on Publications, 1921-1922 (Box 28)
        - Committee on Scholarly Publications
          - 1939-1943 (Box 28)
          - 1947-1952 (Box 28)
        - Committee on Special Needs of the University, 1926-1929 (Box 28)
        - Committee on Storage of Rarities, 1941-1942 (Box 28)
        - Committee on University Archives, 1935-1943 (Box 28)
        - Committee on War Documentation, 1939-1944 (Box 28)
        - Controller
          - 1931-1941 (Box 28)
          - 1946-1949 (Box 28)
        - Correspondence Courses, 1947-1951 (Box 28)
        - Council
          - 1930-1932 (Box 28)
          - 1932-1933 (Box 28)
          - 1933-1934 (Box 28)
          - 1934-1935 (Box 28)
          - 1935-1936 (Box 28)
          - 1936-1937 (Box 28)
          - 1937-1938 (Box 28)
          - 1938-1939 (Box 28)
          - 1939-1940 (Box 28)
          - 1940-1941 (Box 28)
          - 1941-1942 (Box 28)
          - 1942-1943 (Box 28)
          - 1943-1944 (Box 28)
          - 1944-1949 (Box 28)
        - Counselor in Religious Education
          - 1933-1934 (Box 28)
          - 1935-1946 (Box 28)
        - Dean of Administration, 1928-1930 (Box 28)
        - Dean of Men, 1925-1926 (Box 28)
        - Dean of Students
          - 1923-1934 (Box 28)
          - 1935-1950 (Box 28)
        - Dean of Women, 1922-1927 (Box 28)
        - Deans Conference
          - 1923-1926 (Box 28)
          - 1926-1933 (Box 28)
          - 1933-1939 (Box 28)
          - 1939-1941 (Box 28)
          - 1941-1942 (Box 29)
          - 1942-1943 (Box 29)
          - 1943-1944 (Box 29)
          - 1944-1945 (Box 29)
          - 1945-1946 (Box 29)
          - 1946-1947 (Box 29)
          - 1947-1948 (Box 29)
          - 1948-1949 (Box 29)
          - 1949-1950 (Box 29)
        - Department of Engineering Research, 1927-1939 (Box 29)
        - Department of Hygiene and Health, 1922-1940 (Box 29)
        - Department of Library Science
          - 1941-1943 (Box 29)
          - 1943-1946 (Box 29)
          - 1946-1947 (Box 29)
          - 1947-1950 (Box 29)
        - Department of Military Science and Tactics, 1929-1938 (Box 29)
        - Department of Pharmacology, 1943-1944 (Box 29)
        - Department of Physical Education
          - 1933-1940 (Box 29)
          - 1943-1949 (Box 29)
        - Dictionaries, 1935-1950 (Box 29)
        - Director of Plant Extension, 1932-1945 (Box 29)
        - Discipline Committee, 1927-1928 (Box 29)
        - Division of Emergency Training
          - 1942-1943 (Box 29)
          - 1943-1944 (Box 29)
        - Division of Extramural Service, 1936-1942 (Box 29)
        - Division of Fine Arts, 1928-1939 (Box 29)
        - Division of the Biological Sciences, 1949-1950 (Box 29)
        - Dramatic Season, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
        - Elementary School, 1929-1935 (Box 29)
        - Encyclopedia, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
        - Engineering Research Institute, 1947-1949 (Box 29)
        - English Language Institute, 1945-1950 (Box 29)
        - Executive Officers Conference, 1932-1933 (Box 29)
        - Exhibits Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
        - Extension
          - Courses, 1940-1944 (Box 29)
          - Library, 1948-1950 (Box 29)
          - Service
            - 1914-1917 (Box 29)
            - 1922-1925 (Box 29)
            - 1925-1935 (Box 29)
            - 1935-1941 (Box 29)
            - 1942-1946 (Box 29)
            - 1946-1947 (Box 29)
            - 1947-1948 (Box 29)
            - 1948-1949 (Box 29)
            - 1949-1950 (Box 29)
        - Extra-Mural Courses, 1924-1938 (Box 29)
        - Faculty
          - 1912 (Box 29)
          - Notices
            - 1942-1945 (Box 29)
            - 1945-1946 (Box 29)
          - Personnel Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 29)
          - Research Fund, 1927-1928 (Box 29)
        - Fresh Air Camp, 1945-1948 (Box 29)
        - General Library Building
          - 1909-1946 (Box 29)
          - 1946-1949 (Box 29)
          - Blueprints (Box 29)
          - Dedication, 1912-1919 (Box 30)
          - Extension Plans, 1936 (Box 30)
          - Plans (Box 30)
          - Room Assignment, 1948-1950 (Box 30)
          - Specifications, 1915 (Box 30)
        - General Library Council
          - 1934-1935 (Box 30)
          - 1935-1936 (Box 30)